

reza dalvand

Software Engineer

DoB: 1999-08-17 Marital Status: Single

Military Service: Non Medical Exemption

reza.dalvand78@gmail.com

(+98)9032802041

● 11, Shagaig Square, Tayeb St., Iranmehr St., Iranmehr, Khorramabad, Lorestan, Iran

Profile Summary -



Hello, my name is Reza Dalvand. I have been working in the field of programming for several years. I am familiar with the front end (react, next) and worked in the back end (nodejs, nestjs) For 10 months, I worked in a Swedish company as a back-end, of course, the focus was on nodejs, but I also worked on react. I have been in many projects: feedopedia (Nodejs), rewording (Nodejs), plagiarism (Node&react). I worked as a Software Engineer in an Iranian company for 5 months I am interested in learning new things and I am interested in new challenges

Work Experience -



Backend Developer

feedopedia

jönköping, sweden, Sweden

August 2021 - May 2022

Tasks and Achievements

Skills: React.js · Node.js · MongoDB · Cypress · Tailwind CSS · Gitlab

Software Engineer

Wish Work

Tehran, Iran

March 2022 - July 2022

Tasks and Achievements

 \blacksquare Skills: Next.js \cdot matrial-ui \cdot NestJS \cdot graphcms \cdot MongoDB

Education -



Bachelor in Computer Engineering

Branch: Computer Engineering

Institute/University: Islamic Azad university

Khorramabad, Lorestan, Iran

2018 - 2022 GPA: 16.5

Skills -



- node.js, reactjs
- nestjs
- nextjs
- mongo db
- matrial ui
- JavaScript
- GitHub
- Scrum
- Tailwind CSS
- Jira

Language -



English

Reading Level

Writing Level

Speaking Level

Listening Level

Social Network -



- in reza-dalvand-ab7a32206
- oreza.dalvand78@gmail.com
- rezac78

Projects -



feedopedia

For: feedopedia

August 2021

Creating automatic login and register with cypress and debugging the login and register sections and saving information in the database and a few other tasks

Link: app.feedopedia.com

ela

For: wish work

July 2022

Debugging and changing the information, fixing the login section and resending SMS, connecting to the graphems and several other tasks.

Link : ela.store/

haftohasht

For: haftohasht

May 2022

Changing the project from react to next and converting all bootstraps to matrial ui, general debugging and making it responsive, and building a few new pages, such as building the Kenya branch page and shared workspace, etc.

Link: www.haftohasht.studio/